# **LORENA TUHAY**

Software Developer



### **ABOUT ME**

After years of programming as a hobby, I'm currently finishing my degree in Software
Development. I consider myself a self-taught, proactive, curious, and creative person.
Many people I've worked with have described me as highly efficient. I thrive in team environments, as I see them as essential for enriching my knowledge and exploring different ways to achieve objectives.

VISIT PORTFOLIO Ituhay.github.io

### CONTACT

Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina

Email: lorena.tuhay@gmail.com

Phone-WhatsApp: +54 9 11 6160-9490

LinkedIn profile: lorena-tuhay

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Software and Web Developer

2022 - Present

Design and development of static pages and interactive web applications. Configuration of hosting and domain. Creation and maintenance of an ecommerce store using PrestaShop. My expertise is primarily centered around Java Spring Boot, JPA, and ReactJS. I have also worked with WordPress and PrestaShop. Additionally, I have hands-on experience with Python, HTML, CSS, and vanilla JavaScript.

### **Freelance Corrector and Academic Writing Consultant**

2013 - Present

Correction and advice in the drafting and writing of academic texts such as theses, essays, dissertations, and academic reports.

## **Community Manager and e-Commerce manager at Maier FotoPop** 2019 - 2022

Content creation, copywriting, social media management. PrestaShop e-Commerce website design and maintenance.

### **BASIC SKILLS**

Python **HTML CSS** Java JavaScript WordPress React JS **Bootstrap j**Query Hibernate **JPA** Spring Boot **SOL NoSQL** UML OOP **Design Patterns Testing** Functional Analysis Scrum/Agile **GIT** 

### **EDUCATION AND LANGUAGES**

### **Associate Degree in Software Development - UADE**

2021 - Present

Approved courses: 16/20 - Average grade: 8.4/10

### Literary Corrector - Instituto Superior en Letras Eduardo Mallea

2010 - 2013

Average grade: 9.29/10

### **English - Cambridge Institute**

Certificate: First Certificate in English (2004)

Autodidactic level: C2